[Music]
sound to me for your lip
unfiltered Minotaur power
our tale begins in Atlas Brown
Anna when we were together we are
unstoppable
such speed how glorious
the pumpkining of the century
this is Payback
an eye for an eye
for the Crusaders
but they defined technopolka you young
people have no culture at all crunk and
[__] croon the best band of the 2030s
ah even I know that and I've been
trapped in a maze for 800 years
what cc is cheated
you gods and as tough as you seem
I identify if it's a noble rhinoceros
terrible every moment without you
watching over me has been agony
come out and face me
barrier activate it if torbjorn is on my
team then how is he also on the other
team shouting at me
if Linton says one word I swear
honest right a trip to Fiji would be
just a ticket
Ah that's okay we've won the fight
at least I took a lot of them with me
even zarya Nova couldn't save you
you spoil me this is Shields Arya Nova
keep popping back up I don't mind
you know turbian you would make an
excellent Santa Claus
send me a heck will not stop me
hammer down
what is that a toothpick deep breaths
Winston
nobody likes your lava tourbillon
Rally's over
careful where you waves that sword
let's put up a stand here three and out
blessing
blocking
we're in the Red Zone let's punch it in
touch down
he could go all the way
honor I have a glory
My ultimate is ready join me
not quite Genji not quite
what a powerful brawl sorry Angela black
hole or no I'm still swinging looks like
you've been recalled to orbit
punk punk punk
oh that's going to get me a citation
how's that for old man reflexes
since they're jumping around the road I
find it best to just swings a hammer oh
tobian I'll never let you leave that
down
see Jack a hammer is better than a gun
let me show you how it's done
I'm the ultimate crushing machine
stops a payload
ah these old dog still knows a few
tricks
defends the objective
they need a Healer they would be better
served there's a Healer
get out of there
clear the area
catchphrase
My ultimate is almost ready
to see Justice Done is its own reward
ah impressive if I do say so myself
wonderful
so it's done
get ready
Precision German engineering
the 100
German power
I need help
need help here
[Applause]
hey
cold me huh there they go
they went flying land on something soft
express delivery to certain Doom
[Laughter]
14 here
I'll watch this position
I'll keep an eye on that
pushing ahead
onward
let's get moving
over here
Shields up
this way
keep going
follow me our tale begins in atlasbrun
over there
follow me
through here
let me take a swing at that door
time to smash our way through
something needs smashing this is my kind
of mission
help me
someone please
please I need help
stop the robot we must stop them let me
hear mocking the enemy there's the enemy
we're catching up
almost there just a little more
everyone push the lead is almost ours
stay frosty watch here heads up
stay alert
great work mostly me though
no search but I call her Shadow bomb
hey still say shadow bomb has a better
ring to it
they've taken's a robot the enemy has
taken the robot get him back they must
take back the robot he must take back
the lead
so you've pushed ahead of us how
yeah we have lost the lead
there I dropped it
damn I dropped it
strong as an ox
strong as a toxin Maybe
see others are taking the time I see
I can't do this on my own I mean I could
but I don't want to
ah when are my friends coming back
Lucio needs to be revived
someone revive Mercy Serbia needs to be
revived maystone someone needs to help
her Tracer needs to be revived
our Ally needs to be revived
one day you'll pay for all the crimes
you've committed
my elbow Servo isn't actuating God it's
annoying regular
bonuses
[Music]
what did you do you know before was your
crisis
stay behind me I will keep you safe
perhaps we still are
yes but I can't promise I'll understand
it I love car races I octane burning
rubber
um this three loves to Chase
to the metal I don't need two eyes to
swing a hammer either snapping did
anyone read the mission brief let's
attack the enemy from the front and
takes him by surprise
back in my day we had to fight on the
ground
do you intend to be struck in the head
I'll protect your friends
I guess I am
you hear that this channel agrees with
me
he said true
oh no what has been going on in Egypt it
sounds serious
you'll just miss the wind blowing in
your hair
where is it a medic like you learn to
handle a weapon like that
rain out is the name glory is the game
they always worry Anna but I trust you
are doing what is right
says
I'm used to
ah who needs guns let's show them the
classics can still get it done
I heard to show otherwise your life
would be far too easy
how do you think your fancy jumpsuit put
Fair against my hammer do you remember
that night dancing in the command center
until dawn
you have nothing to worry about Captain
you got it
ah perhaps some of us should have guns
no I'm sure brigitta could give you some
pointers
a fine day for charging and hitting
things
I know I know I'm just not very good
with computers
Lake shows his kids how it's done
what are you saying
no I am Reinhard
wilhelmer and shield
Jack my old friends this is going to be
delightful
if I am called and I do not answer
for this left Anna
his balls reconves it together we are
stronger than uh I forget the rest but
it was so inspiring
for you my old friend
of course
Brigitte is the time to size up your
armor it's been ages
all you need for battle is your heart
and your head
somebody's worried he's turning obsolete
Sombra something is wrong with my phone
it is so slow
but I am gloriously fun
complaining already this is what you're
paid for
who's ready to have some fun
I killed many of your kind here Bastion
what
here's my lucky hammer
ah I'm holding it
but thy not aim to be as huge as me
Moira I should crush you like a bug for
what you've done
I never stopped
unlike you
would you like to see my muscles
move the robot
push the robot
ah
they're outnumbered
we are fewer in number but greater in
spirit
are you afraid to fight me
the error is mine
sorry
my apologies
smashing
this is as if it ends Make It Count
this is the final fight let's do
whatever it takes
this will be decided with a trial by
combat
This is Our Moment let us seize it
first one to the objective wins the race
let's get to the objective my friends
get to the objective
no is the objective nearby is this time
my back is killing me
I bet you I could charge all the way to
the objective
[Laughter]
courses cause
lighter than I expected
mine
got it I've got one
bringing the enemy flag back to base
against the flag clear the way
Victory is so close I can taste it
Victory is in our hands this victory has
our name on it hey salute you
all go
the enemy team is eliminated we have the
advantage
except for all of them I was just
getting warmed up you're on my naughty
list
My ultimate is charging
are you chicken
the flag is ours I have claimed the flag
bring me another
face me if you dare
for the Glorious feeling
I am Unstoppable
chat I'm powered up
they must get our flag back
they have stolen our flag
enemy detected
come out are you afraid to face me
stop hiding your coward
you first
yeah
yes
it was worth it
[Music]
taking you with me
enemy Shield generator destroyed
I'm feeling's a burn
I am on fire come face me
you can't stop me I'm on fire
I'm on fire
can you feel the heat
Easy Does It not feeling so good
something's wrong
that is not acceptable
we must not allow that to happen again
oh glittering prices
you're welcome
honor would have me do nothing less
you shame yourself
fortune favors the Bold
respect your elders
dropping the flag
someone take up the flag
I have secured a flag
returning the flag
[Laughter]
Crusader online
that's all your robot suit can do
not on my watch
I don't think so
aren't your dizzy from all that spitting
Victory range from Below
sniper photo you coward
sniper
forgive and forget like snow from
yesteryear
push forward
Reinhardt At Your Service
come to us Trisha Linda you are lagging
behind
don't keep us waiting
Tracer we're waiting for you
Lucio we need you
brigitta this way
get over here
may may over here
hurry up old man
come to us man how did I beat you here
I'm so slow
my barrier won't hold much longer
Barry is about to give
Siberia can't take much more
my barrier is about to break
fall back
[Applause]
I found the enemy's teleporter
someone get to the terminal and get the
heck going no
enemy teleporter destroyed
[Applause]
ah like old times right captain
don't thank me put it on my tab
they stand together my squire
I would never let you fall
you aren't in this fight alone
there's no one on the terminal
the enemy has a shield generator
greetings
hello
my greetings
to keep the heck going
bring on the fight
my shield hold strong
is that all you've got
now we're talking
we are out of time attack
this is a final stand onward
make every second count Crush their
defenses
we don't have much time push forward
have a time goes short but we will not
falter
you're on
this will be a quick Mission if they
aren't
pulled together seize victory
stand your ground and wins a day
hold fast they will not breach our
defense
just a little longer Bear Down
steal yourselves push them back
let's make sure the payload doesn't get
blown up before we get to the door
huh
I found the shield generator
so it's ready to move out
I should have known team get ready for
another wave of attacks
incoming
the enemy is coming through the doorway
I can still learn some new tricks
ha ha
beer
they are forming up
I'm with you
people stand together
I stand with you
our enemies have a teleporter
slices coming in
Percy attack
destroy the objective
behind you
take tether
stop
yo attack the objective Prost
a close shave
that they're back already
watch out they're already back into
fight
enemy is back in the fight
enemy is back for more
I need armor
I need armor yeah more armor
Stallions at payload a few more hits
like that that it's going to blow
that out
oh hi
oh
Ally is laid low
capture the objective
God shut down
ah
a
you were saying
end of the line
duh canceled
you take that
yeah
duh interrupted
huh you cause that big
barrier broken find us a cover bury us
down
you must gather together before we can
continue
defend the flag
protect our flag at all costs
enemy Bastion straight ahead
enemy Bastion on our right
shut up ahead
enemy burst John on the left
enemy Bastion behind us
you forgot to tie your shoes
they all have faith in you tracer
see nothing to worry about rookie
focus on the main targets they're on the
heavy fire
the whole place is going to blow hurry
and destroy the targets this is a team
destroy all Targets come here
the objective is hanging by a thread
Focus your attacks
good keep pushing
we've taken the lead
progress is ours
stops him and it's over
if we're going to stop them we must do
it now
this is our last chance to stop them
stops him and we win
today watch me now ha ha ha look at me
yes yes
sexy sexy right huh oh yes here we go
move your legs and move your arms that
is how we do the dance
yes
oh I love this
this is our last chance defend the robot
almost there we must protect the robot
at all costs
this is the last stretch do not leave
the robot handle that enforcer before
they handle us
take out that Enforcer the robot is ours
come on robot let's go
we've taken the robot the enemy is above
us
they attacked from Zaria the enemy is
behind us cowards
the enemy is below us
are on our right
enemies on the left
they are coming straight for us
the enemy stands before us
we must hold them they are going to take
the lead if we don't stop them
they must not take the lead
we've wounded him don't let up now he's
injured get off me fever stops the enemy
no
they're pushing the barricade stop them
don't let them push that barricade
they need to hurry is somebody going to
get that
someone do the thing
[Music]
ah am I supposed to do something
take her out
someone get her I'm a little busy fetch
me my hammer
she's coming for you
assassins on you looking down
past taken care of
assassin eliminated
that's one annoyance dealt with
coward show yourself
where'd she go done
I've got this one
got it there she is
found a little sneak
so I won't stop that assassin kill the
Assassin already
we are sitting ducks out here if that
payload doesn't get moving fast we are
done for
turbian status update
this is not the type of patience
enforcer eliminated
enforcer down
it all looks so small from up here
I'm over here
reporting in
here's an assassin sneaking around here
watch for an assassin there she is over
there
Tracer try to soften them up this is not
the time tourbillon
slices incoming keeps him off the
payload who's important to pieces
just like in the crisis
watch for that Bastion it's gun will
tear us apart
enforcer get them
there's an enforcer
Unstoppable
recover our flag
get the flag back
let's move the objective out
Detonator left side
Detonator approaching from behind
Detonator heading right at us
a Detonator is bearing down upon us
Detonator right side
defends the objective
good night we are making progress keep
it up
maybe behind my shield
capture the flag
takes the enemy flag
cut the chatter tracer assuming it works
surrounded and outnumbered my kind of
odds
we need to clear them out so torbjorn
can drop in his latest monstrosity
we will not let you down Commander no
sector has three anti-aircraft guns set
up in King's Row
steal yourselves push them back
just a little longer Bear Down
I knew I liked you rookie you're doing
well tracer they didn't doubt you for a
second
don't get him started you'll give him a
big head bigger
good decision
thrill it stay on your guard
they're surrounded the enemy is
attacking from all directions
we even tell that heavy resistance in
the power plant
death later taken care of
destroyed
have no fear I will fight alone if I
must
my allies have all been laid low
I need to be revived
get me back into the fight
I am seriously injured
we are out of time this is our last
chance
we don't have much time push forward
one target left Focus your attacks
for honor and Glory
get over to the payload now
couldn't dream of it captain
team we're heading into enemy territory
for torbjorn of course
stay focused on the mission tracer
they can also revive us if we get too
injured let's take it down
into the garage will hex the first air
defense nodes there
get one ready just in case
I'd recommend staying behind my shield
we each have a tactical drone that can
be used to hack the air defense
terminals
Noble Pursuits both
they could do without the commentary
tourbillon try to avoid that
initiating the hack null Troopers
engaging no Trooper spotted or 14 set up
here
Justice
get back in the fight
I've got your Brigitte it is not your
time yet my friend
stop lying around
come on Tracer super it is not over yet
a flag is free someone grab it safe
dropped a flag return it to base
tobian gets the payload moving out
all right let's move out with the
payload
no Troopers incoming
thousands of payload moving Tracer
torbjorn it's up to us to clear the area
go go take out the window sector troops
inside
we need to take out any null sector
resistance inside
Mercy we're counting on you keep us in
the fight
what are your orders sir how about you
bastards I'll fight the Lord of you
see nothing to worry about
we're done here Captain Amari where's
the next defense node
everyone else good hunting
keep your turret up Eradicator spotted
don't forget about the payload it's
taking damage
go go
Mercy torbjun stay close there won't be
much room to maneuver in there
we're all away captain
we're approaching the cathedral
they're just about to assault the last
Cannon what do we have here
Danka
thank you
much obliged
thank you my friend
thank you
right away
acknowledged
you've got it understood
yes yes
I'm going in
damn
unacceptable
stand behind me friends
I will keep you safe
barrier up
Shield activated
fire at will
I am the champion
what a performance
hardly a fair fight
I'll take you all on
anyone else
[Applause]
yeah
hammer down
goodbye seven
I was wondering if you'd change
something for me it's
um for a friend
it is a reminder of my duty
we fought a terrible battle here many
Crusaders lost their lives
focus on offense drive your enemy back
with the blows from your flail
I have beaten the champion at arm
wrestling
ridiculous stories my Tales have
adventure and Glory are all true
let this be a trial by six
ah Winston it's up to us to keep our
comrade safe
ah could you say that again sometimes
it's hard to hear you all the way down
there
let's show them how it's done
what's wrong with the classics I love
Hasselhoff have you heard night rocker I
remember being posted here it was good
for my turn
protect your teammates make sure they do
not falter just like old times
I will take that as a compliment my lady
a knight could not ask for more from his
choir
she hardly listens to her anyways you
always did take good care of my armor
whose feelings are holiday spirit
agreed let the best man win
I will reclaim my Master's armor do I
have time for a curry first hmm try to
keep me out of trouble
no lesson today show me what you have
learned
they shall prove ourselves in glorious
combat
this is the hometown of my master
baldurick he was born here when he died
here
never I will fight to my last breath
last year I'll show you I'll catch twice
as many as you this year
ah my friends thoughts resources
standing around this glory to be won
so this is Diva's home I expect she'll
have posters everywhere
the old-timers must stick together teach
these kids a thing or two
ah you kids today with your techno music
you should enjoy the classics like
Hasselhoff
I'll probably visit tobian's family in
Gothenburg like the last few years
what an odd compliment
oh you wouldn't believe how hot it gets
in here
I'm ready for some barbecue
that'll be the day
my New Year's resolution same as every
year fight for justice
many of my comrades fell in battle here
Missy rest in peace
you ask that every time and every time I
say no today is no different
stay close to me
too much blood was built in my country
during the war
and you don't know how to stay down when
you're beaten
keep training and maybe someday you
could learn to handle a real weapon
nervous me never
I live for a good fight
who's ready for some karaoke
I'm getting cooked alive in here
and you are looking as lovely as ever
especially that one
your Shield keep yourself from harm they
bear [__] against our enemies
yeah and I sometimes wonder if your
height is why you're always in such a
bad mood
just some bumps and bruises nothing to
worry yourself about
Anna how can this be I thought you were
dead
I remember the poster my hair was
amazing
this is no Castle it's a tomb
like if we stopped get the payload going
violence removing is a payload
can't stop here says glory on the line
let me turret ahead we are not beaten
yet we can still win this
if we gives us everything we've got we
may have a chance
just yourselves or friends this isn't
the end
my friends now is not the time to give
up let us show them our metal
three two fun
in three two one
[Laughter]
on my way
for the Crusaders
finds a teleporter yes
I need Shields never can have enough
I need Shields let's set up here
what magnificent treasure is this
my just reward
a reward for my dedication
a taxi objective
ready
My ultimate is ready
move the payload
eliminate this target
I am a velkmeister of prediction
all in one shot
around the bridge
you're fired Reyes
do I have your attention yet
feel my power
how many was that I am basically a
sniper choose Reinhardt for long-range
destruction
fresh from the oven
even hotter up close
Blended
burned out of the sky
hmm toasted
group up join me
group up here
form up
group up with me
No Doubt
yes ma'am
yes sir let me add some
let's fight
yes
you honor me
[Music]
oh
God oh
God
[Music]
I feel great
back down to earth
not strong enough
whose armor needs fixing now
you can do better than that brigitta
traitor any regrets
feel my power
I slay dragons
try firing more bullets next time
and that is why I still fight
down you go
maybe you should have stepped back
huh and Smash Hit
that is today's lesson
you've been bested
I honor My Vow why don't you
happy holidays
like sorting a fly with a hammer
hardly broke a sweat
that look like it hurt
stay alive and listen
another one for me turbulon you're
losing this bed
retire that
for Baldrick
give me more
that was a bold move
glorious if I do say so myself
that's what happens when you get too
close
still think I'm too old for this
knock you off your feet
by all means try again
no guts no glory
I'm just getting started
maybe you should sit this fight out
one step closer to Victory
door
yo
this armor really needs more padding no
my head
I meant to do that
oh
Shake It Off
go
teaching this single lesson door that
was on purpose
much better
ah I feel like a new man
I will never stop fighting
anyone else
more glory to my name
the fight has just begun
they fall like dominoes
Unstoppable
Ohana it's like we never left
I will take them all on
no lying down on the job
and stay down
it's over for you
Ah that's what I thought
that's what you get for challenging me
don't balls are getting up
defense with me
help me defend
forward this courage
let's show them our strength
stand strong we will not fall
don't worry my friends I will be your
Shield
forward my friends
hold fast do not let them through
I'm looking forward to this
point is ours they must not advance
everyone owns the objective don't let
them take it don't let the enemy take
our point
oh I think I pulled something more
stretching next time
hold a moment I need to catch my breath
oh
I need healing need healing
I can take more than that
maybe I taught her too well
oh Winston my friend you are going to
pay for that I'm not true just yet
there is still more to my tail
I've been knocked down before
there is no challenge I cannot face
the battle Elites me my journey
continues
what's next
I will never Tire up this
still kicking
ha
follow me to Glory
attack
attack this me
enemy turret destroyed
God
go
yeah
ah you thought that would stop me
I'm back
huh what did I miss
thank you my friend
you've come to my Aid again
much better
not obliged
thank you square
oh
foreign
[Music]
Hold the Line
I will hold the line
tobium I will avenge you
our comrade has fallen rally to me
we've got to stop that payload move
together
that payload won't stop itself let's go
stop the payload
together strikes him down
didn't sets feel fantastic
Hara would be proud
well struck Brigitte a commendable hit
I taught her that
well done my friend
you're so great Bella well done my
diminutive Swedish friend
I'm filled with pride
humans are glory for that one your
mother would approve
ah
that shows him why he doesn't pay to
please the enemy
I have found the enemy come and face me
time for a fight make me proud
the payload is under my protection join
me I have control of the payload help me
move it hey moving to payload come visit
me
ah
join me at the objective Glory elates
I'm on the objective stop me if you can
come take the objective with me
ah
[Applause]
for boundary
I am purified
Touchstone
there's no medic nearby no healers
nearby